templaza.com 2016-11-27

# Privacy Policy

##  Privacy Policy 

#### General information

Privacy Policy of TemPlaza is used in order to protect its customers privacy and security of information stored and shared with us through www.templaza.com. This policy explains clearly how we collect , use and maintain your personal information. By registering and using our site you give consent automatically to use and disclose information if needed. Unless you agree with any terms below, you should not use products or services offered by TemPlaza.

#### Information collection and use

It is essential to collect your personal information in order to be able to make any purchase at TemPlaza. It would be impossible to make purchase unless you share personal information with us. It is required to provide us with data in the form of username and password to be able to enter our website. At the moment of registration, you give us consent to send you some informative e-mails. Additionally, your data has to be used while accessing technical support and it is required to make consent to this. Apart from that, in case of issuing invoices or other documents, the buyer is obliged to inform us about his/her detailed personal information; such as name, address.

Except the use of your personal data for administrative and analytical purposes, it is allowed to use it in case of some legal actions. Protection and defense of the rights or property of TemPlaza are taken into consideration, as well as, merger or other business actions.

#### Changing/updating personal data

If you give permission to send you informative messages, including newsletters about product upgrades, updates, new products/services or discounts available, you have to remember about informing us about changing or updating your e-mail address or other changes you may make. If you are unable to make any changes yourself, we can do it on your request. Also, remember about unsubscribing when you do not want to receive any news messages from us as it is possible to do so.

#### Protection of personal information

Information gathered and stored at templaza.com is fully protected. We do our best to secure data collected and do not disclose to any unauthorized person. All data is restricted to TemPlaza employees and external service providers only and they are entitled to use your personal information, however, it is forbidden to misuse this data. If anyone uses classified data in the wrong way, we will take appropriate disciplinary action.

However, we do not take responsibility for data used during PayPal payment as your personal information used there is not registered by our system and has to be protected by PayPal security system.

#### Consent to disclose data

We need to have consent to disclose your personal information because it is impossible to make any purchase without it. If you do not agree to share this data with us, it will be barely possible to offer you any services/ products.

At any time, you may inform us about not willing to share with us your personal information and disclosing it. However, because of that fact our services offered will be restricted. Apart from that, there are some situations where we are forced to use your personal information despite the fact that you withdraw your consent to disclose your information.

#### Contact information

Should the need arise, you would contact us at: [info@templaza.com](mailto:info@templaza.com)

Share It!
